Thank you for watching!
Here we go!
Hello! This time I'll be joined by Ruri Tamura of Juice Juice and Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory.
This time, we'll be presenting you with these two, so please stay with us until the end.
This week, the 17th is Saori Onoda's birthday, which means she will be 22 years old.
Yes, I am turning 22 years old, and I remember that a lot of things happened when I was 21 years old.
I am very good at staying positive and thinking positively every day, like, "Even if this happens, I will do my best next time.
By thinking positively, I have been able to live a very happy life, and I hope to enjoy my 22nd year in a positive way.
I am going to introduce you to the two of us, since we are the same age.
JuiceJuice recently celebrated the final concert of their tour at Nippon Budokan.
This year's concert tour is
We had been touring as part of the 10th anniversary concert tour, and at the time of Yuka Miyazaki's graduation concert Juiceful, we decided to perform all the songs from the past Juice Juice concerts,
We had a concert where we sang a lot of songs, some of them were replacements for others and some were medleys,
This Juice Story concert was the first time we sang a lot of songs from that tour, and we were allowed to do two medleys at the Budokan,
That's right. So I was happy to hear Juice Juice's many wonderful songs.
Tsubaki Factory held the tour final at Nippon Budokan in November, and it was the graduation performance of Riko Yamagishi and Yumeno Kishimoto,
Project, is it very rare for both of them to graduate at the same time?
Project is very rare to have both of them graduate at the same time, so I was very nervous, and I thought it would be a new challenge for their graduation,
I was both excited and anxious about how it would turn out, so I had a lot of emotions,
It was really fun, and the two of them looked so beautiful in their dresses,
I was happy that we were able to end the event on such a happy note, and I hope it will lead to future events,
I think we were able to end the Nippon Budokan concert in a way that will lead us to the future.
I think we were able to make it a Nippon Budokan performance that will lead to the future,
I think we were able to make it a Nippon Budokan performance that will lead to the future, and I am very happy that I was able to go and see it,
I was also able to go and see the concert,
Thank you very much.
It was a very happy space, and I felt very happy too.
Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us will be held from January 2 next year.
We are different teams,
TIPAKI FACTORY is team A.
JUSTUS is team B,
Project's concert at the beginning of the year,
Project as a whole,
Project as a whole, which has been very rare in recent years,
Project as a whole, so I would like to take this opportunity to see the wonderful aspects of the various teams and learn from them,
Project as a whole, so I would like to take this opportunity to see and study the wonderful things that different teams have to offer,
Project as a whole.
Please come and visit us.
We are doing our best.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please watch it.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching.
We can't take a break, so let's not let you guys take a break too.
Let's launch the show anyway, so that you don't see anyone in love.
Oh, no!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
on
on me
Втор
Lyrics, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
I don't care who you talk to or what rumors you hear, I don't care
Hey, be more confident Hey, be more like yourself
Hey, shine more brightly Hey, me
My heart is dancing, I'm starting to see tomorrow
GO! On top of a dream, in the midst of making something GO! On top of a dream, something, seize the future
On top of the dream, in making something GO! On top of the dream, seize the future
The heart becomes the owner The heart becomes the owner
There were definitely days when I felt like I was going to break down and lose.
Looking back, there were troubles that made me laugh
My life has begun
If it were easy, I'd cry.
It's not a fantasy, it's real
Hey, you can trust me more Hey, you can be straighter
I can flap my wings more Hey, I can flap my wings more Hey, I can flap my wings more
My heart is singing
It's starting to show now
Go, follow your dreams What's gonna happen?
Go, follow your dreams What's the future hold
Go, follow your dreams, what's gonna happen
Go you never end
Why don't you hold on to the future
My heart is dancing
It's jumping out at me
I'm starting to catch tomorrow
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Enjoying it? Watch the rest of the show.
Ganbare Lulu of Juice Juice and
and Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory.
We're going to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So please answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Yes, I'll do my best.
It's been about a month since Tsubaki Factory was reorganized.
How do you feel your role has changed?
I think I have to work harder.
Looking back on the year 2023, what is the best kanji character for you?
It is the character for graduation.
December is when I made my debut as a trainee 9 years ago.
What is the biggest difference between yourself then and now?
My personality.
What is your favorite Tsubaki Factory song?
Smile
What are you personally interested in now?
Movies.
Thank you.
That's all.
Looking back on the year 2023, the perfect kanji character for the year is "graduation," so...
Yes, that's right.
We had three members graduate in the year 2023.
I see, I see, Harumi too
Nozomi Asakura also graduated, so
When three members graduate, it really changes the atmosphere of the group
Now the four younger members
are already half of the group.
I'm sad to see the older sisters of the group graduating.
but I think we will be able to take on new challenges.
I'm looking forward to doing my best.
I'll be rooting for you.
I'll do my best.
Also, I like many of Tsubaki Factory's songs.
I'm so happy!
I wanted to listen to a song that Saori Onoura likes, so I asked her about it.
She said "Smile".
Yes, the song "Smile" is your favorite, isn't it?
Yes, the song "Smile" is one of my favorites, isn't it?
I think the title of the song is very positive and cheerful.
It really makes me happy just by singing it.
This song is not only a happy song, but also a fun song.
If you think about the meaning of the lyrics, I think there is a deeper meaning to the song.
I think the lyrics can be taken in different ways by different people.
I hope you will listen to the song and feel positive about it.
I'll give it another listen.
Questions for Ms. Dambala will follow the VTR.
Halostei
Angulum Red Line Nowown Scion
Angsturm, Life is Beautiful.
Angulum Red Line Now on Scion
Now please listen to the last song.
Momoyoji Sou no Kisekiwa
My favorite town, I've been dancing
Strolling with my new friends
The changing times, the places I want to go
Made me realize the dream that won't change
We overcame those tantalizing days together, that's why
I promise you tomorrow I'll be okay with the powder storm
Promise, Kakato level
Even if my hands jump, if I'm with you all
I'll walk on with a smile, I promise, I'm not afraid of the maze
Promise, light shining, pull me along
I wonder if I touched it, a smudge, a mist
Open up, open up
Words, music, arrangement by Masaru Yamaguchi
Gentle gusts of wind, the old man's clapping, he'll give you a warm welcome.
I can't hold on to my dreams, I'll make them come true, my journey never ends
I want to fill up the whole map with my favorites
I've promised the past, I've promised the past, I've promised the past, I've promised the past, I've promised the past, I've promised the past, I'll choose with you, if it's a rainbow
Surprise, surprise, enjoy, smile
Promise to the past, promise to the past, promise to the past, promise to the past, promise to the past, promise to the past, promise to the past
Ticket, two floors up, we're going to push on
Yes, I met you, you
A painting of a painting
Promise me tomorrow I won't let any storm get in my way
Promise, if there's a port with real feelings, I can aim for it
I'll chase you to the end of the rainbow
Wow promise everything is just one night
Promise, I wish
Let's unite our hearts and burn together
Changing the world's promise
From the big invitation, believe in the promise
I'll pull you along
I can see it in one day for one year
Miracle of Soul, Let's Talk About It
JuiceJuice TEN'S ANNIVERSARY CONCERT TOUR 2023 FINAL JUICETORY has ended!
Thank you very much!
I feel like I just met you, but let me tell you what I think of you!
Well, JuiceStory means "History of Juice",
I was trying my best to convey the meaning of the title to you all,
I was really enjoying the singing voices that showed the excitement of the audience as they sang directly into my ears,
I also learned that many of you were enjoying yourselves and crying a lot.
I was happy to know that JuiceStory is able to move people's emotions. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
We have been on this tour for a long time,
It changes day by day,
Yes.
We performed a medley of the songs that we had changed each day during the tour and presented them at the Budokan,
I was very happy to be able to do this medley, as it was something we had not done very often,
I was also happy to perform the medley. I think it is quite a feat to perform on the Nippon Budokan stage three times a year,
I also think it's quite a feat to perform on the Nippon Budokan stage three times a year, and I feel that the stage is filled with a lot of our history,
Juice again for the 11th year. I had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Holds.
Next, I would like to ask you a question.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
You've been a sub-leader for about two years.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you look back on this period?
Mr. Kamimura is amazing.
What would you like to do now?
Acoustic live performance.
That's amazing!
What trends are you noticing this winter?
I like turtlenecks.
What is the best compliment you receive?
I am happy when I get compliments on my smile.
What is the biggest event for JuiceJuice in 2023?
Our 10th anniversary!
Wow, thank you so much!
All of the questions had wonderful answers.
What do you think is great about Akari Uemura?
What do you think is especially great about Akari Uemura?
Me and...
I have a different way of thinking today.
I often think that we have different ways of thinking and that we are quite opposite.
The most important thing is that she is very free.
I think it's great that you're so cheerful and happy every day.
I think it's wonderful.
I feel like you share your brightness with everyone.
I feel like you share your brightness with all the members.
Thanks to you, Mr. Uemura, the team is very bright and happy.
I think it's because of you that the team is so cheerful and happy.
I think it's important to be cheerful at all times.
I think it would be possible for anyone to be so cheerful at all times.
I think it's great that you are so energetic all the time, which is something that anyone would be able to do.
You are a wonderful leader.
I admire that.
That's great.
Now, I have a question that's been bothering me.
What words of praise make you happy?
I asked this question myself.
Thank you very much.
Yes, you do love to smile, don't you?
It makes me happy when someone compliments me on my "I love you.
It's nice. It makes me happy when I get compliments on my singing or dancing or performance.
I'm very happy when I'm praised for my singing or dancing or my performance, but the most is when people say that my smile cheers them up.
I do this job to cheer people up, so I'm very happy when people say they love my smile.
Thank you very much.
Hello! Stay tuned for more after this!
Natsuyaki Niyabi!
It's time for Hello Kitchen!
This time we have a member here.
This is Ayume from 17 Snacks!
I will do my best!
I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please give my best regards to you today, doctor.
Thank you very much.
Now, doctor, what would you like to make today?
Yes, I am. Speaking of Kudo-san, octopus.
Oh!
So, I'm going to make octopus pasta with fishing.
Oh! That's nice.
Fishing style, I'm so happy.
It's very seasonal and fun.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. Here are the ingredients.
So, let's see, Kudo-chan likes octopus,
I heard that you have been involved in fish-related activities recently.
That's right. I, Kudo, was recently appointed by the Director General of the Fisheries Agency as a member of the Fish Day Cheering Squad,
Fish Day is a day when the Fisheries Agency hopes that everyone will eat a lot of marine products,
The Fisheries Agency has designated the 3rd to 7th of every month as Fish Day in order to encourage people to eat more marine products,
It's 3 and 7.
Since the 3rd to 7th of every month is Fish Day, I hope you will eat a lot of fish,
I hope you will eat a lot of fish.
Yes, I know.
The day was established to encourage people to eat fish,
So this time, fish.
Well, octopus is not really a fish,
It is a fish.
So, I was included in the fish group,
I am sure of it.
I want to eat a lot of fish.
Oh, I want to cook.
Yes, I do.
Let's eat and cook.
Yes. Let's do our best.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
What would you like to cook first, doctor?
Well, let's see.
We need to make the tomato sauce first.
First, the tomatoes.
You have to scrub the tomatoes.
And then...
Here we go.
There's some left here.
It's such a waste.
Just like the SDGs.
If you fill it with water like this...
If you do it like this...
You'd think the water would dilute it.
But I'll boil it down, so it's totally fine.
I see.
It's beautiful.
It's not grainy anymore.
It's smoother.
Like a definitive texture.
Yes, it is.
But much more.
finish a little bit at all.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
I have a trick.
I keep trying to do the same thing here.
It gets stuck.
I'm going to shift it around a bit.
You can still see a lot of things.
It's such a different landscape.
It's about time.
It still looks like tomato juice.
It looks like tomato juice.
By boiling it down...
Yes.
The acidity of the tomatoes turns to sweetness.
The color also changes.
Next...
Chop the onions.
This may be the most difficult part of the day.
That's right.
Core on the other side.
Yes, that's right
1 cm in
Yes, in width
I don't know...
It looks like it's attached to the tip.
Sorry.
Kokkokokokokokokokokokokokokokokokokokoku
No, no, no...
Oh, nya!
Good evening.
He's cute.
A little more.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
I cared too.
Just a little colder.
That's it.
If it's here, how do I cut it?
Just cut it right here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That part's easy.
Just do it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's right.
Oh, nya.
Yes, it is.
Ah, nya.
Yes, okay, okay.
It's done.
Okay, here's what we're going to do next.
Garlic.
Yes, I'll use it.
Yes, sir.
We'll use two cloves of garlic.
Garlic.
You like garlic?
Yes, I love it. I love it so much.
Good.
It's good with octopus.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it's good.
When you pull it out, split it in half.
There's a core in the middle.
Yes.
Take this out.
And the garlic.
Yes, sir.
This is not enough.
Yes.
You should crush it.
This is different from smacking, right?
I'll do it like this.
It's easier to hit like this.
Oh.
More like that.
Don.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Practice has begun.
LOL!
LOL.
Practice hard.
You're already crushed enough.
Yes, sir.
That's fine.
How can this pair
It's so strange.
I've never seen anything like it.
This feeling
I see.
Yeah.
There's not much excitement.
Ever.
Next, we're going to start the process of frying the garlic.
Yes, sir
It smells good.
It's crushed.
At first, let the olive oil warm up a little bit.
High heat.
When it starts to puking, turn down the heat a little.
and when it starts to puking, lower the heat a little bit to low.
Let the aroma of the garlic transfer to the oil.
Mmmm...
It was like a sizzle.
Like fried food.
Yes, that's right.
When it gets like this, turn it down a little bit.
And if you do it like this, the garlic
The head comes out.
So it's hard for the aroma to come out.
Put it down.
It's getting burnt. We'll turn off the heat a little more.
The oil is still hot, so we'll preheat it.
Put the flavors back in.
Then add the onions.
The pan is still hot.
Yes, it's still hot.
I don't know if this is in the recipe, but...
Okay.
A teaspoon of olive oil.
A teaspoon.
For the onions
Yes, sir.
Then fry this.
Now, here's the point of the Palace Fire Diagram.
The onions should be the color of the sister.
Yes, sir.
This is an important point.
It's very important, isn't it?
Yes.
This is important for everything.
I can't believe I'm saying this.
Rain-colored.
We're going to go beyond candy.
More than candy.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
It's coming.
Yes, it's coming.
Yes, it is.
That's a good idea.
And then I mix it all up so that it's all turned over nicely.
It's a little more silky, a little more transparent, and a little more colorful.
Yes, sir.
It's a little moist.
How's the aroma?
It's getting fragrant.
See?
Here it is.
This is it.
This is the decisive factor in cooking.
That's an important point, isn't it?
Important point.
Yes.
I'm also a fish day supporter.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to try my hand at cooking fish.
Yes.
What kind of fish dishes do you want to cook?
Well, the other day I used simmered fish.
That's nice.
You want to try your hand at cooking it?
Yes.
I'd also like to try my hand at grilling fish to make it fluffy and delicious.
Do you have any tips?
Um...
Fluffy?
Fluff?
Yes.
You need to put a little water in the fish grill, you know, the one that's in every household these days?
There are a lot of grills these days that don't have water in them, but they're actually fluffier if there's water in them.
Down there.
That's right.
So you put a little bit of water in a heat-resistant cup or something, and then grill them together.
Ah...
Moisture comes up from the bottom.
And then it comes up.
Wow!
Steamed
Steamed and baked
Yeah.
It's a little fluffy, isn't it?
I see.
But it looks good?
Yes.
It has color, doesn't it?
It's fragrant.
Well, then, you can leave the onions here, because I just made you choose...
I did my best to get him to choose.
I'll give you the tomatoes.
And then...
Here.
We're going to use the tomatoes from earlier.
How long does it take to cook them?
About 10 to 15 minutes.
Now they're dry, aren't they?
We'll make it thicker.
It's not sludge, it's thicker.
So, about 15 minutes.
That's right.
After 10 to 15 minutes of boiling...
What was smooth and silky just now...
It's a little heavier now.
It becomes thicker.
It's like a sauce that's been roasted.
I don't know how to say this.
It's a little oily, isn't it?
Now that the moisture and...
Moisture is gone.
And the sauce is ready for the ice cream.
Yes, sir.
So this is the end of making the sauce.
Next time, it will be finished.
I can't wait to see it!
Let's do our best!
Please look forward to the next time!
I'm really looking forward to the completion. I'm looking forward to it. I wonder how it will turn out.
It looked delicious.
Do we usually cook?
I don't cook,
I don't cook, but there are many times when I think that Mr. Danbara is a very good cook.
But since it is winter, I think everyone eats a lot of hot pot,
I also really like to cook and eat hot pot,
I make a pot with a lot of Chinese cabbage,
I make pots with a lot of Chinese cabbage, and I made an earthenware pot.
You also make earthenware pots?
You mean the earthenware pots you make?
I made earthenware pots at a pottery class, and now I am using them myself,
I made it with Akari Uemura,
She invited me to join her, and she seems to like ceramics.
She has a great hobby.
She invited me to make these pots, and I got to make them with her,
I made them myself, and I love them because I made them myself,
You get attached to them, don't you?
Yes, I want to use it a lot,
I would like to eat a lot of hot pots this winter, too.
I want to eat your homemade nabe, too.
I really love motsu-nabe.
I understand.
I wish you could make it for me someday, I thought as I was listening to you just now.
Let's eat it.
This is Haloste, presented by Gambaralulu of Juice Juice and Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory.
This year 2023 is the 25th anniversary of Hello Project, so here is a live video of the first time we performed a song of our choice from the 25-year history of the project.
I performed Fiesta Fiesta for the first time at the Hello Project concert in the summer of 2017.
This was when I joined Juice Juice and performed it for the first time at my first live concert,
This was the first time I received the song "Fiesta Fiesta," and the first song I sang was "Unleash Your Passion,
After I sang the song, the people who came to the concert cheered and said, "Wow!
That made me very happy,
I still remember how happy I was,
I still remember how happy it made me, so I chose this live video to watch again.
It gave me goosebumps.
I remember it too.
It was amazing.
Well, I don't know,
I heard that Juice Juice was going to have new members for the first time,
So Nana Yanagawa and I joined the group,
I was very anxious about it,
When we stood on the stage,
I was so nervous,
I was very nervous and had a lot of mixed feelings,
I was very happy to hear your appreciation.
Juice Juice
Piesta Piesta Piesta, let's unleash our passion!
Piesta Piesta, woman is always so, Maria of the trap
Hand to hand, hand to hand, if you love me, I'll be beautiful.
Hand to hand, hand to hand, skin to skin, it's up to you
The next live video I chose to perform the song for the first time was performed at the First Live House Tour in 2018
Happy Cracker" from our first live house tour in 2018.
This was the first time Tsubaki Factory toured live house.
But there are not many videos of the live house tour.
So I think this Happy Cracker video is very valuable.
So I think this Happy Cracker video is very valuable, and I hope that people who didn't know about the live house tour period will be able to see it.
It's so fresh and new.
Yes, they are.
There are so many scenes where I'm there and I still think they're so cute and fresh.
I'm thinking about how they used to be like this.
I'd be happy if you could watch it.
I hope you enjoy the show.
Thank you for watching.
You are the only one I love
I won't let anyone get in the way
Embraced by the Shabbos of love
Only you for me
If you're about to cry, cry, cry
See, all love is a soap bubble
If you're in love, this sin
Love in your own name
Soap bubbles
Wow, wow, wow
You're the only one I love
But it turns out there's no girl, no girl, just a base.
Of all the girls in the world.
What's my ranking?
Waiting is not the end of the world
All love is like soap bubbles
If you fall in love, this is your sin
You'll have to fall in love with me, chef-on-ma'am.
You said you really wanted to hear it!
I'd do anything for you.
Tell me what's wrong with you, okay? Right?
What are you talking about when people take you so seriously?
I'm all ears.
You want me to be the only one who knows about it, don't you?
Of course you do. You like him.
Yeah, give me a hug. Give me a hug.
Cry if you have to
All love is a soap opera
If you're gonna fall in love, next time
You'll be in love every day of your life
Cry if you can, cry if you can't
All love is no soap
All love is not soap.
I want you to do it. Do it.
Soap bubbles
Why don't we take it easy today?
Dambara Jul of Juice Juice and Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Juice Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
Juice Juice at Budokan is now on sale on Blu-ray DVD!
Juice Juice has performed at Budokan 3 times this year.
This May's Budokan concert was the first one.
This is the first time in a long time that we have been able to perform at the Budokan.
It was also the first time in a while that we could hear many voices of Juice Juice family at the concert.
I hope you can see that moment.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
And I will be performing with Janoma at the Cho-Idol Fest on December 21.
I will be performing with Janoma at the Cho-Idol Fest on December 21.
The live performances against other bands always give me a lot of inspiration.
Please do your best as Juice Juice!
We look forward to seeing you there!
Tsubaki Factory will perform at Idol Wave in Tokyo on December 29th.
Idol Wave In Tokyo on December 29th.
Tsubaki Factory is now a 9-member group.
We will do our best so that you can enjoy the current Tsubaki Factory to the fullest!
And on December 30th and 31st
Hello Project Year End Party 2023
Goodbye & Hello will be held!
December 31st will be held simultaneously in Tokyo and Osaka!
Oh, that's great!
Oh, wow!
So Juice Juice will perform in Osaka
Tsubaki Factory will be performing in Tokyo, so
Please join us in Osaka or Tokyo to enjoy the end of the year 2023!
And as for the New Year's Concerts
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us will start on January 2nd!
Tsubaki Factory will perform as Team A and Juice Chus as Team B!
We hope to have a great time with you at the Meiji concert.
We are looking forward to seeing you in 2024!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we're joined by Danbaralulu from Juice Chus and Saori Onoda from Tsubaki Factory!
Good bye!